{"data":[{"question":"The ships had their days of ________ in the 1840s and 1850s.","a":"glorious","b":"glory","c":"glorify","d":"gloriously","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Proposition + Noun\/ Verb-ing.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Tea loses its flavor quickly ________ in the hold of a vessel.","a":"when storing","b":"stored","c":"when stored","d":"storing","answer":"3","explain":"\n- What\/where\/ which... can be use as a relative pronoun. Relative pronouns introduce relative clauses, which are a type of dependent clause.\u00a0\n- Dependent clause followed by relative pronoun (who\/whom\/which\/where...) is narrative sentence: S + V + O.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Earl was one of the first American artists ________ landscapes.","a":"painting","b":"painted","c":"for painting","d":"to paint","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Structure: the first, the second (time\/person...) to do sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The crime rate has continued to rise in American cities despite efforts on the part of both government and private citizens to curb ________.","a":"them","b":"him","c":"its","d":"it","answer":"4","explain":"\n- It= crime rate (singular).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"In 1778, he ________ to London to study with Benjamin West for four years.","a":"has gone","b":"had gone","c":"would go","d":"went","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Simple past tense: Use the Simple Past to express the idea that an action started and finished at a specific time in the past (in 1778).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"No one has been able to satisfactorily explain how or ________ the Moon sporadically sparks.","a":"when","b":"why","c":"what","d":"which","answer":"2","explain":"\n- In the blank, we need a \"reason\"- why.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The basic fiber-optics system is called a fiberscope, ________ consists of two bundles of fibers.","a":"which","b":"in which","c":"where","d":"what","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Which: used, after a comma in writing, to add more information about the thing, situation, or event you have just mentioned.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Physicians can look into the lungs, heart and other areas that were formerly ________ to them.","a":"accessibly","b":"access","c":"accessible","d":"inaccessible","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Inaccessible(adj): difficult or impossible to reach","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"________ his highly individual conceptions of music and chaos, John Cage became a leading figure in avant-garde music.","a":"Such was","b":"Due to","c":"Because from","d":"That","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Due to= because of sth.\u00a0\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Sanford Meisner ________ the Neighborhood Playhouse in New York City.","a":"founding and directing","b":"who founded and directed","c":"founded and directed","d":"in finding and directing","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Narrative sentence: S + V + O.\u00a0\n\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}